Hey, new wallet?
새 지갑이네?
It was time.
바꿀 때가 됐어, 해묵은
콘돔이 거처를 옮겨 달래
The old condom ring in the leather
just doesn't say "cool" anymore.
Rachel, you just put an empty carton
back in the fridge.
레이첼, 빈 통을
왜 냉장고에 넣어?
쓰레기통이 꽉 차서
I know,
but the garbage was full.
Have you ever taken out the trash?
- 너 쓰레기 버린 적 있니?
- 그럼!
Since you've lived here?
여기 산 이후로는?
Well, I thought you liked doing it.
네가 즐거운 마음으로
버리는 것 같아서
-Third door on the left.
-Right!
- 왼쪽으로 세 번째 문
- 알아!
쓰레기 투입구
Hey, Mr. Treeger.
- 안녕하세요, 트리거 씨?
- 네
위험물 투기 엄금
What are you doing?
뭐하쇼?
I'm sorry.
죄송, 좀 오래됐지만...
It's a little old but....
됐소, 30분 동안 뚫어놨는데
또 막으면 어쩌자는 거요?
You're clogging up the chute
I just unclogged.
I'm sorry.
I don't come in here a lot.
죄송해요
하도 오랜만에 와서
그렇겠지
공주님이시니까
Of course not.
You're a little princess.
Daddy, buy me a pizza.
'아빠, 피자 사줘요'
'아빠, 사탕공장 사줘요'
Daddy, buy me a candy factory.
Daddy, make the cast of Cats
sing "Happy Birthday" to me.
'아빠, 캣츠의 주인공들이
내 생일축가 부르게 해줘요'
이렇게 난장판을 쳐놓고
관리인한테 맡기면 다요?
You think you can come here...
...make a mess and a big man
in coveralls will clean it up?
다른 사람한테
부탁하지 그러쇼
Think of someone else for a change.
Okay, I'm sorry.
미안하다구요
야, 그런다고 우냐?
God, if you're going to cry about it!
The One With Ballroom Dancing
Treeger made you cry?
- 트리거가 널 울렸어?
- 그래
He said really mean things
that were only partly true.
진짜 심했어
반만 진실인데
I'll teach him a lesson.
- 손 좀 봐줘야겠군
- 그냥 덮어두는 게 좋겠어
Joey, don't.
Let's forget about it.
그런 말 쉽게도 나오지?
누군 죽을 뻔했는데
That's easy for you to say.
You weren't almost just killed!
All right, that's it.
School is in session!
말리지 마, 수업 시작됐어
- 이거 체육관 카드야?
- 그래, 회원이거든
Is this a gym card?
Oh, yeah, gym member.
원래 일주일에 네 번 가는데
1,200번 빠졌어
I try to go four times a week,
but I've missed...
...the last 1200 times.
So why don't you quit?
그만두면 되잖아
You don't think I've tried?
나라고 용을 안 썼겠어?
You think I like having $50 a month
taken from my account?
누구는 매달 50달러씩
빠져나가는 게 좋겠어?
They make you go
all the way down there.
보통내기들이 아냐
They use all these phrases
and peppiness to confuse you.
온갖 사탕발림으로
사람 혼을 뺀다고
And then they bring out Maria.
게다가 마리아까지 나타나
-Who is Maria?
-Oh, Maria!
- 마리아가 누군데?
- 오, 마리아...
You can't say no to her.
그 쫙 달라붙은 라이크라
스판덱스를 어떻게 거부하냐?
She's like this lycra,
spandex-covered, gym treat.
Do you need me to go with you
and hold your hand?
- 내가 같이 가서 도와줄까?
- 아니
You're strong enough to face her?
- 혼자 할 수 있다고?
- 아니, 같이 가자
Oh, no. You'll have to come.
Tribbiani.
Hold on.
트리비아니
기다리게
'뚫어펑' 가져오지
I'll get the plunger.
이거 보쇼
You hold on.
You made my friend Rachel cry.
내 친구 레이첼을 울렸으니까
당장 올라가서 사과하세요
So you'll go and apologize to her...
집주인한테 알리기 전에
...unless you want me
to call the landlord.
뭘 알려?
And tell him what?
여자를 울리지 말라는 얘기
못 들어본 모양이군요
Maybe you haven't heard of
"not making girls cry."
1968년에 제정된 주택임대
안정법을 모르는 모양이군
Maybe you haven't heard of the
Rent Stabilization Act of 1968.
그딴 건 잘 모르겠네요
I have actually not heard of that.
Your friends are violating it.
자네 친구들은 법을 위반했어
여태 참았지만 도저히 안되겠군
I've been nice until now,
but I don't need this grief.
I'm telling the landlord...
모니카의 불법임대 사실을
집주인에게 알려야겠어
...Monica's illegally
subletting her grandmother's place.
Your friends are out of here, pal.
이젠 나가야 될 걸
Why don't you tell me
something I don't know?
다 아는 거 강조하지 마쇼
오늘 정말 일 나가기 싫다
Somebody tell me
I don't have to work today.
What's the matter?
왜 그래?
너무 근사한 마사지 손님을
받았는데 그 사람 볼 때마다
My first massage is
this incredibly gorgeous guy.
Every time I see him,
I want to...
공짜로 뭔가를 해주고 싶어
...do things to him
I can't charge for.
So do them for free.
그럼 공짜로 해주렴?
No, it is forbidden.
그건 규정에 어긋나
Mrs. Potter fires people
for messing around with clients.
손님이랑 눈 맞혔다간
바로 해고야
And it's against my oath
as a masseuse.
안마사 선서에도 어긋나고
- 선서까지 했어?
- 아니, 스스로 한 거야
-They make you take an oath?
-No, I made myself take one.
No fooling around with clients...
손님이랑 놀지 말고
늘 준비태세를 갖추자
...and always be prepared.
That one's from the Boy Scouts,
but it just makes good sense.
보이스카우트 선서지만
꽤 쓸만하잖아
다른 안마사한테 돌리지?
Why not give him to someone else?
프로가 그 정도도
관리 못해서 쓰나
No, I can handle it.
I'm a professional.
Pheebs, is that
a new ankle bracelet?
그건 못 보던 발찌네?
You got a pedicure.
페디큐어에다
발 치장 근사하다
Your feet are all dressed up.
손님이 테이블에 올라가면
그 부분밖에 안 보이니까
That's the only part he can see
when he's on the table!
발로 새롱거리는 여자!
You're going to do
some feet flirting!
I don't know what
you're talking about.
무슨 소린지 모르겠네
How do you explain the toe ring?
그럼 발가락 반지는 뭐야
It's Arabian Princess Day at work.
Leave me alone!
'아라비아 공주의 날'이거든
나 좀 살려주라
나의 영웅!
어떻게 됐어?
My hero! What happened?
내 친구한테 사과하라고
윽박질렀지, 이따 보자
I told him no one treats
my friends like that.
And he better apologize.
See you!
Wait a minute.
잠깐
What did he say?
그랬더니 뭐래?
He wouldn't apologize because
you're living here illegally.
너희는 불법거주자라
사과하기 싫고
Instead, he'll evict you.
See you later!
강제퇴거 시킨대
이따 보자
- 강제퇴거?
- 내려가지 말라고 했지?
-You got us evicted?
-I told you not to go down there.
- 레이첼을 울렸잖아
- 얘는 툭하면 울어
He made Rachel cry!
Rachel always cries!
That's not true!
내가 언제!
You go down there,
and you suck up to him.
내려가서 싹싹 빌어
You suck like
you've never sucked before!
손발이 부르트게 싹싹 빌어
All right, I'll try.
알았어, 해볼게
If I can't, you stay with us
till you get settled.
안되면 당분간
우리랑 같이 살자
- 출동!
- 알았다니까
-Go!
-All right, all right.
I'll have to check first,
but he'll be cool.
시간 지나면
가라앉을 거야
Remember what we talked about.
You got to be strong.
아까도 얘기했지만
마음 단단히 먹어야 돼
그래, 알았어
Now one more time.
복습하자
Don't you want a washboard stomach
and rock-hard pecs?
'돌처럼 단단한 근육을
원하지 않습니까?'
No, I want a flabby gut
and saggy man-breasts.
'아뇨, 축 처진 가슴과
뱃살이 더 좋습니다! '
That's good.
- 아주 훌륭해
- 그래
I want to quit the gym.
여기 그만두렵니다
You want to quit?
그만두신다구요?
I want to quit the gym.
고만 다닐래요
You do realize you won't have
access to our new Swedish spa?
그럼 저희 스웨덴식 온천도
이용할 수 없게 되는데요?
I want to quit the gym.
그만두고 싶네요
Dave in the membership office
handles quitters.
좋습니다, 담당인
데이브한테 가보시죠
Excuse me.
Are you a member?
실례지만 회원이세요?
Me?
저요?
아뇨
Sorry. Members only.
죄송하지만
비회원은 안 됩니다
I want to quit the gym!
그만둘 거야
괜찮아, 확 밀어붙여
It's okay, man.
Be strong.
다니시는 체육관 있나요?
Are you a member of any gym?
No, and I'm not going to be.
So save your little speech.
전혀 생각 없으니까
서로 시간낭비 맙시다
Okay, no problem.
그건 염려 마시고,
잠깐 이리 와봐
Could you come here?
Hi, I'm Maria.
안녕? 마리아예요
네에...
힐링 핸즈
공인 안마시술소
You have really pretty feet.
와우, 발이 참 예쁘군요
These old things?
낯 뜨겁게스리...
Would you spend time on my
sciatic area? It's killing me.
좌골 쪽 좀 만져주시죠
통증이 심하군요
You mean....
좌골 쪽이라 하심은
타월로 덮인 부위?
By sciatic, you mean...
...the towel-covered portion?
네
Sure, I can do that.
그럼요, 물론 해드려야죠
Because the muscles
in the sciatic area can get...
좌골 근육은 잘만 하면
끝내주게 탄탄해지거든요
...real nice and tight.
So tell me, Rick,
how did you injure the area?
저기, 어쩌다 좌골 쪽에
상해를 당하셨는지요?
A 16-hour sit-in for Greenpeace.
16시간 동안 그린피스에서
연좌농성을 했더니
아우!
-Did you just bite me?
-No!
- 방금 깨물었어요?
- 아뇨
뭔가!
Please don't kick the girls out.
This was my fault.
모니카랑 레이첼은
아무 죄가 없어요
You want me to kick
you guys out instead?
대신 자네들을 쫓아낼까?
You can't. Where would
the chick and the duck live?
그럼 오리하고 병아리는
어디서 삽니까?
You have pets?
동물을 기르나?
아뇨, 별말씀을...
Those are nicknames.
그건 우리 별명이에요
난 병아리, 챈들러는 오리
I'm the "chick,"
and Chandler's the "duck."
I would've thought
it was the other way around.
그 반대인 거 같은데
제발 쫓아내지 마세요
뭐든 시키는 대로 할게요
Come on.
Let the girls stay.
I'll do whatever you want.
Really? You'd do anything?
정말인가? 뭐든?
Yeah, absolutely.
네, 그럼요
I got something.
- 해줄 일이 있긴 한데
- 그게 뭔데요?
What is it?
Can you be my dancing partner?
댄스 파트너가 필요해
That's not prison lingo, is it?
감방 전문용어 아니죠?
I want to quit the gym.
그만둔다고 했슴돠!
Can you honestly tell me that you're
100% satisfied with your body.
선생님의 신체에 100%
자신이 있다는 겁니까?
Yes, yes. Most of the time.
그럼요, 대부분은
I mean, sure, I have my bad days, but
then I remember what a cute smile I have.
안 좋은 날도 있지만
미소는 늘 귀엽죠
We were voted "Best-equipped Gym
in New York" two years running.
저희는 2년 연속 최우수
체육관으로 선정됐는데
-Do you really want to give that up?
-Yes, I hate it here.
- 그걸 포기한다구요?
- 난 여기 싫어요
Everything that you have
in here is very heavy.
여긴 무거운 것밖에 없잖소
네
Really? Okay?
정말?
알았어
You want to make your
friend work out alone?
친구를 두고 떠나진 않겠죠?
-What friend?
-Your friend Ross. Just joined.
- 친구라뇨?
- 친구 분이 방금 등록했군요
댄스 파트너?
His dancing partner?
관리인 무도회가 있대
'수퍼볼'이라고
There's this superintendents' dance,
"The Super Ball."
몰래 흠모하는 마지한테
잘 보이고 싶은가 봐
He wants to impress Marge,
this lady super he likes.
여자랑 연습하지?
Why not practice with a girl?
수줍음이 많아서 아직
여자하고는 곤란하대
He's too shy.
He's not good enough
to dance with girls yet.
그래, 까딱했으면
나 쓰레기통에 뛰어들었어
Yeah, right.
He almost danced me right down
that garbage chute.
Would you let it go already?
You're fine.
그만 잊어버려, 괜찮아
So did you quit?
취소했어?
I almost did.
아니, 문턱까지 갔는데
로스가 외로울 것 같아서
Couldn't leave Ross there
without a spotter.
Wait, now, so you joined the gym?
너까지 등록했어?
And that's funny, why?
그게 왜 우습지?
I was just, you know,
picturing you working out, and....
너 운동하는 모습을
상상하니...
Well, that's it.
그거야
We're doomed.
일났다, 평생 매달 50달러씩
갖다 바치게 생겼어, 어쩌지?
They'll take $50 a month from our
accounts for the rest of our lives.
What are we gonna do?
체육관에 나가
You could actually go to the gym.
아니면 은행계좌를 해약해서
돈줄을 원천봉쇄하는 거야
Or we could go to the bank...
...close our accounts
and cut them off at the source.
You're a genius.
넌 천재야
Oh, man! But then,
we won't be bank buddies.
우린 계좌 동료잖아
Now there's two reasons.
이유가 하나 더 늘었다
You guys, remember that cute client
I told you about?
얘들아
아까 얘기했던 손님 있지?
내가 깨물었어
I bit him.
-Where?
-On the tushy.
- 어디를?
- 엉덩이
And that's not against your oath?
그건 선서에 어긋나지 않아?
I know,
but the moment I touch him...
알지만 그 몸을 만지는 순간
선서를 확 내팽개치고 싶었어
...I want to throw out my old oath
and take a new, dirty one.
Next time, try to distract yourself.
앞으로는 다른 생각을 해봐
그래, 흥분되는 일을 할 때
너무 흥분하고 싶지 않으면
Like when I'm doing
something exciting...
...and I don't want to get too...
...excited.
I try and think of other things.
Like sandwiches...
나도 딴 생각을 하지
가령 샌드위치
아니면 야구
...and baseball...
아니면...
...and Chandler.
챈들러
-Thank you.
-Oh, no, thank you.
- 고맙다, 조이
- 아니, 네 덕분이야
All right, I'm here.
Let's get this over with.
나 왔어요
빨리 끝내죠
Okay, well...
그래, 내 리드만 따라와
...just follow my lead.
준비운동은 필요 없나요?
엉망으로 취한다든지
Don't we need to do some kind
of preparation first?
Like get really drunk?
Come on. Hey, just put
your arms around me.
팔을 내 어깨에 둘러
미안하네
I'm sorry.
No. It's okay.
But if I'm Marge...
아니, 괜찮아요
하지만 내가 마지였다면
가슴이 등으로 튀어나왔어요
...my breasts are coming out my back.
Forget it!
I'm not being any good at this.
그만두세, 역시 무리였어
엄마 말씀이 옳았어
난 팔다리만 달린 감자야
My mom was right.
I'm just a big potato
with arms and legs and a head.
감자라니 무슨 말이에요
Come on, man.
You're not a potato.
댄서는 더더욱 아니지
내 주제에 마지를 넘봤다니
I'm sure as hell not a dancer.
It's no use.
Marge will never go for me.
못난 소리 말아요
연습이 부족한 거죠
Come on, Treeger.
Don't say that.
You just need more practice.
자, 다시 해봐요
Come on.
Let's try it again.
어서
Plus, it was probably
mostly my fault anyway.
아마 내 잘못이 클 거예요
남자랑 춤추는 건... 휘히!
I'm not that comfortable
dancing with a
So how goes the dancing?
Gay yet?
댄스는 어땠어?
아찔하지?
You guys owe me bigtime.
나한테 신세진 줄 알아
What was that?
그건 뭐지?
뭐?
그건 댄스잖아
You just did a little dancy thing.
-No, I didn't.
-Yes, you did.
아냐
- 맞아, 스텝을 밟았어
- 너무 좋아한다
-You did a little hop.
-You are so enjoying this.
천만에
No, I'm not.
And it wasn't a hop.
It was a pas de bourree.
스텝이 아니라
'파 드 부레'야
You know the words!
용어까지 꿰고
체질인가 보다
You are so into this!
Maybe I'm enjoying it a little.
I'm getting pretty good at it.
재미는 좀 있더라
소질도 다분하고
귀여워라
우리 앙증맞은 춤꾼
This is so sweet.
Joey, our little twinkletoes.
이건 여자애들 춤이 아니라
남자다운 스포츠야!
This isn't some kind of girly dance.
It's like a sport, it's manly.
-Show me some "manly" moves.
-All right.
- 그 남자다운 동작 좀 보자
- 좋아
I don't know how to lead.
리드할 줄은 몰라
Hello.
안녕하세요
We'd like to close our accounts.
계좌를 해약하려구요
Close your accounts?
Is there a problem?
계좌를 해약해요?
문제가 있습니까?
- 아뇨
- 그냥 해약하고 싶어서요
No, we'd just like to close them.
좋습니다, 해약 담당은
램버트 양입니다
Ms. Lambert handles all our closures.
Would you come over here, please?
잠깐 이리 오세요
Hi, I'm Karen.
캐런이에요
I want to quit the bank!
은행 관둘래요!
Okay. Baseball.
그래, 야구다
릭이 야구를 한다
Rick playing baseball.
He slides into second.
2루에서 슬라이딩
바지가 좀 내려온다, 안돼!
Maybe even his pants
come down a little.
좋아, 그럼 샌드위치
Okay, sandwiches.
Sandwiches.
Okay, on a plate.
접시 위에 있다
Maybe Rick's pants come down a little.
바지가 좀 내려온다, 안돼!
챈들러...
Chandler.
Okay, Chandler.
That's working!
옳거니, 효과가 있네?
Chandler's knees.
챈들러의 무릎
Chandler's ankles.
챈들러의 발목
챈들러의 발목 털
Chandler's ankle hair.
Oh, no!
오, 이런
Okay, you're all set.
끝났습니다
정말 대단하군요
Wow! That was amazing!
Was that really just an hour?
- 벌써 한 시간이 됐나요?
- 네
In really long-hour world.
정말 길군요
What?
네?
말하죠
I have an enormous crush on you.
전 그쪽이 너무 좋은데
But since you're a client,
I can't ask you out...
손님이라 만나자고는 못해요
느낌이 찌릿하게 오지만
...even though you give me
the feelings.
I had no idea.
그건 전혀 몰랐는데요
다른 안마사를 찾으면 되죠
I can always find another masseuse.
Really?
- 정말이에요?
- 그럼요
Yeah, really.
What?
왜요?
Suddenly I'm very aware I'm naked.
갑자기 몸이 허전해서
Quiet down.
시끄러워요
사이먼 씨가...
어머나
Mr. Simon's been waiting
Oh, my God!
Why wasn't I offered that?
난 저런 거 없나요?
비용이 더 들어도 좋소
I'd definitely pay more for that.
We have rules here.
This is not that kind of place.
업소 방침을 잊었어?
여긴 그런 데가 아냐
하지만 그건 오해예요
릭은 제 남편이거든요
I know, but this isn't
how it looks at all...
...because Rick is my husband.
그래?
Oh, really?
부인이란 여자가 세 번이나
전화해서 남편을 찾았어
You'd better tell his other wife.
She called three times
asking where he is.
Yes, I will tell her.
네, 제가 그 여자한테 말하죠
은행 거래를 못 끊었어?
So you didn't leave the bank?
그래, 어쩌다보니
공동결제계좌까지 생겼네
And somehow we ended up
with a joint checking account.
What will you ever use that for?
그걸 어디다 쓰게?
To pay for the gym.
체육관 회비 납부용?
환상적인 날이야
So I had a great day.
릭이랑 꿍짝이 잘 맞았는데
창녀 노릇한다고 짤렸지 뭐야
Rick and I hit it off.
We were making out.
Then my boss walked in
and fired me for being a whore.
뭐?
- 해고당했어?
- 세상에
-You got fired?
-Oh, my gosh!
It's so weird. I have never
been fired from anything.
해고당한 건 난생 첨이다
Sweetie.
저런...
I started walking around,
not knowing what to do next.
하도 막막해서
정처 없이 걷다가
I started asking people on the street
if they wanted massages.
사람들한테 마사지
받겠냐고 물었더니
경찰도 날 더러 창녀래
Then these policemen thought
I was a whore too.
It's really been a bad day,
whore-wise.
오늘 창녀 기분 꽝이다
Hey, Duck.
Is Chick here?
이보게, 오리
병아리 있나?
Yeah, Bunny Rabbit.
네, 산토끼 버니 씨
Ready for our last practice?
최종연습이 남았죠?
We're not getting that spin right
because my place is too small.
내 방이 너무 좁아서
스핀이 제대로 안 됐어
-Want to use our place?
-No, I had another idea.
- 우리 방으로 갈까요?
- 아니, 다른 생각이 있어
해냈어요!
We did it!
성공이야, 놀랍구만!
That was incredible!
That was amazing!
We totally nailed it!
네, 마무리까지
너무 완벽했어요
정말 고맙네, 트리비아니
Hey, listen.
Thanks a lot, Tribbiani.
Oh, my God!
Look at the time.
저런, 시간이 벌써...
이러다 버스 놓치겠어
I got to catch the bus to the ball.
그래요
행운을 빌어요
Good luck.
Unless you want to practice
the fox trot. Or the tango?
폭스트롯이나 탱고
한 번 더 땡길래요?
Thanks, but no.
고맙지만 사양할게
여자랑 춤출 준비 끝났어
You see, I think I'm ready
to dance with girls.
좋아요
- 한 수 보여줘요
- 그래
-Go get them, Treeger.
-Right.
저기... 함께 갈까?
마지 친구가 있는데
You want to come?
Marge has a friend.
Really?
정말요?
그럼, 잘 어울릴 거야
나랑 사이즈가 똑같아
You'd dance good with her.
She's the same size as me.
포기하죠
No, I'm good.
라라 & 젠 안마시술소
It looks like you've got
great experience.
경력이 화려하군요
보자... 지난번 직업을
그만둔 이유는?
Let's see.
Reason for leaving last job?
They thought I was a whore.
제가 창녀 같대요
Okay. We'll give you a call
if anything comes up.
좋아요, 자리 비면
연락드리죠
Great. Thank you very much.
감사합니다